BABYMETAL DEATH!
B!
B A!
B A B!
B A B Y!
B A B Y  M!
B A B Y  M E!
B A B Y  M E T!
B A B Y  M E T A!
B A B Y  M E T A L!
DEATH!
I am SU-METAL!
I am YUIMETAL!
DEATH!
I am MOAMETAL!
We are BABYMETAL!
B!
B A!
B A B!
B A B Y!
B A B Y  M!
B A B Y  M E!
B A B Y  M E T!
B A B Y  M E T A!
B A B Y  M E T A L!
DEATH!
I am SU-METAL!
I am YUIMETAL!
DEATH!
I am MOAMETAL!
We are BABYMETAL!
DEATH!
GYAH!
I am SU-METAL!
DEATH!
I am YUIMETAL!
I am MOAMETAL!
DEATH!
We are BABYMETAL!
If we open the secret box
We can fly off anywhere
It's a mint-flavored time machine
We can go anywhere
Our hour, Bubble ball fever!
Our bubblele, Bubble ball fever!
Bubble ball, Bubble ball fever!
Ah Yeah!
Fly off, chu, chu, chewing gum!
Oh yeah!
Ah Yeah!
Let's go! Go, go, going up!
Oh yeah!
Ah Yeah!
Fly off, bap, bap, bubble gum!
Oh yeah!
Ah Yeah!
Right now, go, go, going now!
Oh yeah!
If we open the secret lock
We can fly off anywhere
With the swelling dream, riding on the wind
We can go anywhere
Our hour, bubble ball fever!
Our bubblele, bubble ball fever!
Sing it!
Fly off, chu, chu, chewing gum!
More!
Oh yeah!
Let's go! Go, go, going up!
More!
Fly off, bap, bap, bubble gum!
Oh yeah!
Thats Good!
Right now, go, go, going now!
Oh yeah!
One! Two! Three! Four!
One!
One! Two!
One! Two! Three!
One! Two! Three! Four!
One!
One! Two!
One! Two! Three!
One! Two! Three! Four!
One!
One! Two!
One! Two! Three!
One! Two! Three! Four!
One!
One! Two!
One! Two! Three!
One! Two! Three! Four!
If we open the secret room
We can fly off anywhere
In the dream, in the dream
We can go anywhere
Our hour, Bubble ball fever!
Our bubblele, Bubble ball Po! Po!
Bubble ball, Bubble ball fever!
Sing it!
Fly off, chu, chu, chewing gum!
Oh yeah!
More!
Let's go! Go, go, going up!
Oh yeah!
Try harder!
Fly off, bap, bap, bubble gum!
Oh yeah!
Last one!
Right now, go, go, going now!
Going now!
Ah Yeah!
Chewing, chewing, chu, chu, chewing gum!
Oh yeah!
Ah Yeah!
Bubble, bubble, bap, bap, bubble gum!
Oh yeah!
Ah! Dreamer!
Let's turn off the light
and charge ourselves with energy!
Now seems to begin
A hilarious midnight
Let's write serious and read it as really
It's time to get hyper
under the sparkling mirror ball
Squid, squid. I want to eat squid arms!
I prefer dried squid
No, no. It makes you like a middle-aged man
Why don't we choose cute sweets?
Hey, boys and girls
Pack lots of your sweets and your dreams
Now gather in my house!
It's a party night!
You and me
You and me!
Tonight is a cheerful
Hilarious midnight!
Curfew!
Closing time!
No, no, non!
No way!
It continues still more!
Glittering bright!
Let's turn off the light
and charge ourselves with energy!
Now seems to begin
Sing!
A hilarious midnight!
Let's write serious and read it as really!
It's time to get hyper
under the sparkling mirror ball!
Hilarious midnight!
Hey, boys and girls!
Eating lots of the sweets and the dreams!
Now jump out of my house!
It's a party time!
You and me
You and me!
Tonight is a cheerful
Hilarious midnight!
Curfew!
Closing time!
No, no, non!
No way!
It continues still more!
Glittering bright!
Let's turn off the light
and charge ourselves with energy!
But now is coming...
The climax!
My eyes get bleary, I rub them and Really?
Let's get hyper!
Glittering bright!
Let's turn off the light
and charge ourselves with energy!
Now seems to begin...
Sing!
A hilarious midnight!
Let's write serious and read it as really!
It's time to get hyper
under the sparkling mirror ball!
GYAH!
M E T A!
Meta Taroh! Meta Taroh!
You are the hero!
With the Metal heart
You're going to be reborn
Meta Taroh! Meta Taroh!
Together boys and girls!
He's everybody's hero!
META! Meta Taroh!
M!
M E!
M E T!
M E T A!
M!
M E!
M E T!
M E T A!
META!
Long ago, long long ago
Far away
META!
In a clear planet in the galaxy
He was born!
It's the period of war! Winners enjoy heaven!
We always lose and our life is hell!
Now we will say farewell to those days!
Now let's stand up!
Can you hear the voice from inside of you?
Can you hear the voices of your comrades?
Hit it away, Meta Taroh!
Meta Taroh! Meta Taroh!
You are the hero
With the Metal power
you're going to be reborn!
Meta Taroh! Meta Taroh!
Together boys and girls!
He's everybody's hero!
META! Meta Taroh!
M!
M E!
M E T!
M E T A!
M!
M E!
M E T!
M E T A!
Sing it!
Everybody sing it!
Can you hear the voices of your comrades?
Call the hero up from your heart!
Meta Taroh! Meta Taroh!
You're the Metal hero
If Metal music sounds
We are friends!
Meta Taroh! Meta Taroh!
Together boys and girls
Everybody, let's sing together!
META! Meta Taroh!
He's everybody's hero
Me
Meta
Meta Ta
Meta Taro
Meta Taroh!
I dislike!
Guys who think only about themselves
You're uncool, super uncool!
Don't approach me!
I dislike!
Impossible! Useless! It's reached the limit!
They're uncool, super uncool!
I don't wanna hear them!
I will knock your ill-nature into shape
Burn! Burn!
Your anger hidden inside!
Stop kidding! Hey, you!
It doesn't matter to win or lose
It is only to be serious or not that matters!
I dislike!
I dislike! dislike!
I dislike! dislike! dislike!
I dislike! dislike! dislike! dislike!
Fight!
Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
You, stupid guy!
I dislike!
Guys who are not serious but only make excuses
Stop kidding! I get super irritated
Don't turn your dirty face to me!
I dislike!
Guys who can't do it but pretend to be tough
Stop kidding! I get really irritated!
Get out of my sight!
I will beat your ill-nature into shape
I will burn up everything
With the flare of anger!
Stop kidding! Hey, you!
It doesn't matter to be skillful or awkward
You may think back but may not regret!
Fight! Fight!
Against sneaking temptation!
Shout out your anger!
Stop kidding! Hey, you!
You say sorry? You say forgive me?
What do I do with you?
Stop kidding! Hey, you!
It's a lie? Flattery?
Ready for anything!  Bring it on!
Going over thousands nights
Some love shall survive
So, until my body perishes
Until my life disappears
I shall keep on cherishing this love
I'ts the dawn!
Shining in the depths of the eyes
the moon is about to cry
Red tears overflow
And dye the night sky
In the silence
The two damaged blades stand face to face
Our loneliness and our uneasiness
Slash even our hearts
Going over thousands nights
Some love shall survive
So, until my body perishes
Until my life disappears
I shall keep on cherishing this love
In the passage of time
I keep my eyes shut
Even if the red thread flowing in my hand breaks
I still feel we are tied
In the silence
I hold the damaged blade face to face
My loneliness and my uneasiness
I slash, even my heart
Now!
Going over thousands nights
Some love shall survive
So, until my body perishes
Until my life disappears someday
Going over thousands nights
Some love shall survive
So, until my body perishes
Until my life disappears
I shall keep on cherishing this love
Dye crimson! Dye bloody crimson!
Tactic 1
I flatter more than usual
I give Dad a shoulder massage, and immediately...
I love you, Dad!
Tactic 2
Thank you for your hard work. You are my god
Of course my favorite type is...
I love you, Dad
Lies are alright!
No need to restrain!
Keep on praising!
Flattery, flattery!
I want that one!
A little more bolder!
I want this one too!
With angel's face, devil's whisper!
Rather than preaching, give me the money!
I will become your bride, Dad!
Let's go! Let's go!
Beg-Dad-for-it operation!
Make a cute sulky face and keep on claiming!
The strongest!
Oh!
The greatest!
Dad is about to be cheated by my angelic smile!
Let's go! Let's go!
Beg-Dad-for-it operation!
I will get it in secret from Mom
The strongest!
Oh!
The greatest!
I beg! I beg!
Beg-Dad-for-it operation
I entreat! I entreat!
This is the last
Always
If I marry, I will marry after all...
You, Dad!
I entreat! I entreat!
This is the last
Always
I play the spoiled kid
BLACK BABYMETAL!
I entreat! I entreat!
This is the last
Always
Once in my lifetime!
The first and the last
I entreat! I entreat!
This is the last
Always
I play the perfect little devil!
BLACK BABYMETAL!
Because I am a girl!
I love sparkling things!
I love cute things!
I love delicious things!
One for the money!
Two for the money!
Three for the money!
Money! Money! Money! Money!
One for the money!
Two for the money!
Three for the money!
Money! Money! Money! Money!
One for the money!
Two for the money!
Three for the money!
Money! Money! Money! Money!
One for the money!
Two for the money!
Three for the money! money! money!
Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
I beg!
I beg! I beg!
I beg! I beg! I beg!
I beg! I beg! I beg! I beg!
I beg!
I beg!  I beg!
I beg!  I beg!  I beg!
I beg!  I beg!  I beg!  I beg!
Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
I beg!
I beg! I beg!
I beg! I beg! I beg!
I beg! I beg! I beg! I beg!
I beg!
I beg! I beg!
I beg! I beg! I beg!
Let's go! Let's go!
Beg-Dad-for-it operation!
Make a cute sulky face and keep on claiming!
The strongest!
Oh!
The greatest!
Dad is about to be cheated by my angelic smile
Let's go! Let's go!
Beg-Dad-for-it operation!
I will get it in secret from Mom
The strongest!
Oh!
The greatest!
I beg! I beg!
Beg-Dad-for-it operation
I entreat! I entreat!
This is the last
Always
If I marry, I will marry after all..
You, Dad
I entreat! I entreat!
This is the last
Always
I play the spoiled kid!
BLACK BABYMETAL!
I entreat! I entreat!
This is the last
Always
Once in my lifetime!
The first and the last
I entreat! I entreat!
This is the last
Always
I play the perfect little devil
BLACK BABYMETAL!
Why can't I sleep?
Why does the night end?
I don't want anything, even tomorrow
The future without you
Why was I smiling?
Why so though I was feeling lonely?
Nobody knows that I really just
Wanted you to be by my side
Even the despair becomes the light
Though an endless rain continues to fall
A sad rain throws a rainbow
Far far away
We shall never meet again
But I want not to forget you forever
If the dream continues, I wish I'll never wake up from it
Why was I smiling?
Why so though I was feeling lonely?
Nobody knows that I really just
wanted to see you That was all
Even the despair becomes the light
Though an endless rain continues to fall
A sad rain throws a rainbow
Even now!
An endless rain fills my heart
Forever!
Good Morning! Wake up!
A thump-thump-beating morning
Ah!
Straight! Straight! My bangs end makes a straight line
It's a cutie style
After all, a really straight line shall get the first prize
It's super-awesome!
Today's lip-gloss shall be that? This? That? Which?
Which? Wait! Watch! What time is it now?
Gathering! Gathering! Gathering after school
It's a party time!
Don't you know the girls-only gathering and the girl talk?
It's super-exciting
Today's VIP will be over there? Here? There? Where?
Which? Wait! Watch!
Sing!
What time is it now?
Pretending not to know, I dislike
The world I don't know yet, I want to see
Four-dimensional and five-dimensional worlds, I anticipate
Ten percent higher, I want to go
You too, don't you?
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Good Morning! Wake up!
Please! Wait a moment! Wait a moment!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Don't be hasty! But hurry up!
A hectic, busy morning!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Take your time to make up!
Please! Wait a moment! Wait a moment!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Today I improved!
A thump-thump-beating morning
No make-up! No make-up!
My glasses serve as hair-pins
It's a funny face!
But wait three seconds! I finish changing!
It's super-quick
Today's rap music will be that? This? That? Which?
Which? Wait! Watch!
Come on!
What time is it now?
Pretending not to know, I dislike
The world I don't know yet, I want to see
Four-dimensional and five-dimensional worlds, I anticipate
Ten percent higher, I want to go
You too, don't you?
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Good Morning! Wake up!
Please! Wait a moment! Wait a moment!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Don't be hasty! But hurry up!
A hectic, busy morning!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Take your time to make up!
Please! Wait a moment! Wait a moment!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Today I improved!
A thump-thump-beating morning!
GYAH!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Good Morning! Wake up!
Please! Wait a moment! Wait a moment!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Don't be hasty! But hurry up!
A hectic, busy morning
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Take your time to make up!
Please! Wait a moment! Wait a moment!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Today I improved!
A thump-thump-beating morning!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Good Morning! Wake up!
A thump-thump-beating morning!
I'm a fox, I'm a fox, I am a female fox
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Dressed-up Miss Fox
Ting-a-ling! Cheer up!
Ting-a-ling! Cheer up! Ting-a-ling! Cheer up!
Waves her twin ponytails in the air
Fluttering! Cheer up!
Fluttering! Cheer up! Fluttering! Cheer up!
She pops and vanishes
Whirling! Cheer up!
Whirling! Cheer up! Whirling! Cheer up!
Let her show her various aspects!
Kon
Kon kon
Kon kon kon
Kon kon kon ko
Kon
Kon kon
Kon kon ko
Kon kon ko kon!
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Ancient maidens
You dance in the transient dream
Getting over thousands years
You live today
Ah!
it's right. Always women are actresses
We're not foxes, not deceiving
But maiden-like female foxes
Ah!
Girls are becoming more like an ideal woman
Smiling at face, crying at heart
Saying It's right we never show our tears
Fox, fox, I'm a female fox.
Women are actresses
Are you ready?
Are you ready tokyo dome?
Everybody clap your hands!
I couldn't hear you at all!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
One! Two! One! Two! Three! Four!
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
More!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Ancient maidens
You sing in the transient dream
Getting over thousands years
You live inside us
Ah!
it's right. Always women are actresses
We're not foxes, not deceiving
Maidens...
Shouldn't be underestimated
Ah!
Girls are becoming more like an ideal woman
Continuously, to keep blazing
We shoot up the fireworks
Ah!
Blooming and falling is the fate for a woman.
Smiling at face, crying at heart,
We're pure-hearted maiden-like female foxes.
Ah!
With the legendary black long hair
Disordered around and gorgeously
Blooming crazy, this flower
Will soon disappear fruitlessly
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Bang
Bang bang
Bang bang ba
Bang bang ba bang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Bang
Bang bang
Bang bang ba
Bang bang ba bang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Bang
Bang bang
Bang bang ba
Bang bang ba bang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Now the time has come
I no longer hesitate
I hold tightly
The discount railway tickets
To the east, to the west
To the south, to the north
Today too I rush to the very front of the stage center
On the left side
Come on!
On the right side
Standing up still, leaning back
Jumping toward the stage
And then!
Leaning over the fence
Rolling over the mob
And then!
And then all deeply headbanging
This special night of my fifteen
I'll never forget
All the crybabies
Get out of here!
With the legendary black long hair
Disordered around and gorgeously
Blooming crazy, this flower
Will soon disappear fruitlessly
It'll never come back again
And it's so short period
I etch in my heart
This special night of my fifteen
I jump lightly and dance in the air
Headbanger!
Headbang! Headbang!
More! More!
Everybody make sure to look!
Headbang! Headbang!
??
Head! head! head! head!
This special night of my fifteen
I'll never forget
All the crybabies
From here
Dis-ap-pear!
This special night of my fifteen
I'll never forget
All that disturb us
right now get out of here!
With the legendary black long hair
Disordered around and gorgeously
Blooming crazy, this flower
Will soon disappear fruitlessly
It'll never come back again
And it's so short period
I etch in my heart
This special night of my fifteen
With the legendary black long hair
Disordered around and gorgeously
Blooming crazy, this flower
Will soon disappear fruitlessly
I can never come back again to it
And it's so short period
I etch in my memory
This special night of my fifteen
I jump lightly and dance in the air
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Bang
Bang bang
Bang bang ba
Bang bang ba bang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbanger!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang!
Headbang! Headbang! Headbang!
Ah!
Dreaming, I couldn't have even it.
Between the light and the darkness
I stayed alone
Those who got hurt were
not only I myself
but also those who kept on watching me
It was you
Confidence
Have it!
I couldn't have
Don't be beaten!
I kept on hiding
I dislike to be found!
Until yesterday
Yesterday is gone!
But good-bye to yesterdays' myself
Bye-bye!
Bullying
No!
It's disgraceful!
No! No! No! No!
Sometimes you get hurt
Sometimes you hurt someone
And we all get badly hurt
Fox
Fly!
I'm sure you can fly
Fly! Fly! Fly! Fly!
Let your pain and sadness
All go outside!
It's OK because I'll protect you
I didn't show my tears
And in the night I was about to cry
In a room deep inside my heart
I stayed alone
Those who hurt me were
Not only someone else
But also those who pretended not to notice
It was my friend
Nothing
Nothing!
Could I say
Say nothing!?
I was about to give up
No easy throwing out!
Until yesterday
Yesterday is gone!
But good-bye to yesterdays' myself
Bye-bye!
Bullying
No!
It's disgraceful.
No! No! No! No!
Sometimes you get hurt
Sometimes you hurt someone
And we all get badly hurt
Fox
Fly!
I'm sure you can fly
Fly! Fly! Fly! Fly!
Let your pain and sadness
All go outside!
It's OK because I'll protect you
Pain...
Aching...
All the while...
Alone...
Your heart...
Pretending not to notice...
Anymore...
I'll never get away
Bullying, No, Absolutely
Full of dearest-ness
it's pressuring
But also encouraging
Anymore...
Anymore your...
I don't want to see anymore your tearful face
Tokyo Dome!
Bullying!
No!
It's disgraceful!
No! No! No! No!
Sometimes you get hurt
Sometimes you hurt someone
And we all get badly hurt
Fox
Fly!
I'm sure you can fly
Let your pain and sadness
All go outside!
It's OK because I'll protect you
Bullying, No, absolutely!
No! No! No! No!
Bullying, No, forever!
Bullying, No, absolutely!
No! No! No! No!
Bullying, No, never!
We are?
BABYMETAL!
Three! Two! One!
Subtitles by  x I A l e x a n d e r I x